Office of Community Relations Records UA233
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Subject files, 1971 -- 2016; UA233.002; 7.5 Linear Feet 7 record cartons and 1 letter size document box
  Transferred by the Office of Community Relations, 2018, accession UA-2019-005.
  The majority of the subject files are arranged alphabetically. Files created specifically by former Community Relations Director Barbara Rubel are arranged in received order in a separate sub-series.
  This series contains subject files created or collected by the Office of Community Relations and former Director Barbara Rubel. Topics include Tufts buildings; policies; committees and associations within and outside Tufts; events and programming within Tufts and within neighborhood communities; construction projects; and Tufts presidents. Formats of materials include correspondence, financial reports, maps, notes, and publications. This series also contains awards received by the department and aerial photographs of Medford, MA. Content of subject files may overlap with that of campus files and project files.
  - Advertising, 2003 -- 2016; UA233.002.004.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - AICUM (Association of Independent Colleges and Universities in Massachusetts), 2010 -- 2015; UA233.002.004.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Art Gallery, 1995 -- 2008; UA233.002.004.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Athletics, 1982 -- 2012; UA233.002.004.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Boston Higher Education Partnership, 1983 -- 2006; UA233.002.004.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Buildings and construction, 1983 -- 2012; UA233.002.004.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Census, 1984 -- 2015; UA233.002.004.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Census 2010, 2010 -- 2011; UA233.002.004.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Mystic River Watershed Association, 2001 -- 2013; UA233.002.004.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Construction - Chinatown, 2010 -- 2015; UA233.002.004.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Construction - Chinatown, 1991 -- 2009; UA233.002.004.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Construction - Medford 1, 2006 -- 2010; UA233.002.004.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Construction - Medford 2, 2004 -- 2007; UA233.002.004.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Construction 574 Boston Ave., 2012 -- 2015; UA233.002.004.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Construction - Boston Ave., 2013 -- 2016; UA233.002.004.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Construction - Somerville 1, 2011 -- 2014; UA233.002.005.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Construction - Medford 5, 1995 -- 2016; UA233.002.005.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Somerville 2, 2014 -- 2015; UA233.002.005.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Campus, 2004; UA233.002.005.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Campus 2, 1986 -- 2005; UA233.002.005.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Capen Street, 1995 -- 2000; UA233.002.005.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Chemistry department, 2008 -- 2011; UA233.002.005.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Child development, 2000 -- 2001; UA233.002.005.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Community gardens, 1987 -- 2002; UA233.002.005.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Community relations, 1976 -- 2016; UA233.002.005.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Community reports - Chinatown/Boston, 1992 -- 2014; UA233.002.005.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Community reports - Medford, 1983 -- 2015; UA233.002.005.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Community reports - Somerville, 1985 -- 2015; UA233.002.005.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Dental School, 1991 -- 2011; UA233.002.005.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Dogs on campus, 1999 -- 2012; UA233.002.005.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Donations - non-monetary, 2009 -- 2011; UA233.002.005.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Economic impact study, 1980 -- 1990; UA233.002.005.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Eliot-Pearson school, 2000 -- 2009; UA233.002.005.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Engineering, 2011 -- 2015; UA233.002.005.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - EPIIC (Education for Public Inquiry and International Citizenship), 1995 -- 2001; UA233.002.005.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Evacuation plans, 2000 -- 2001; UA233.002.005.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - ExCollege, 2009 -- 2012; UA233.002.005.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Farm proposal, 2011; UA233.002.005.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - The Giving Camp, 2002; UA233.002.005.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Grafton, 2004 -- 2016; UA233.002.005.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Greek life, 2010 -- 2012; UA233.002.005.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Health sciences - master plan, 1991 -- 1997; UA233.002.005.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Health sciences - master plan II, 1990 -- 1997; UA233.002.005.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - High school auditing, 1996 -- 2001; UA233.002.005.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Institutional biosafety committee, 2014 -- 2015; UA233.002.005.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - LCS K2C continued, 2001 -- 2007; UA233.002.006.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Kids to college, 1993 -- 1999; UA233.002.006.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Kids to college, 2007 -- 2010; UA233.002.006.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Kids to college, 2011 -- 2015; UA233.002.006.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Let's get ready, 2014; UA233.002.006.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Letters - neighbors, 1995 -- 1999; UA233.002.006.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Licenses, 1980 -- 2011; UA233.002.006.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Local schools, 1980 -- 202; UA233.002.006.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Mass highway signage, 2009; UA233.002.006.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Medford parks and recreation, 2015; UA233.002.006.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Medical school, 2009 -- 2013; UA233.002.006.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Minors policy, 2012; UA233.002.006.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Museum school, 2008; UA233.002.006.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Jan music concerts, 2007 -- 2012; UA233.002.006.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Music dept., 2001 -- 2011; UA233.002.006.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Neighbors, 2015; UA233.002.006.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Occupational Therapy dept., 2013; UA233.002.006.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Off campus brochures and posters, 2011 -- 2014; UA233.002.006.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Off campus living, 1986 -- 2012; UA233.002.007.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Campus living, 1998 -- 2015; UA233.002.007.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Pilot payments, 1980 -- 2006; UA233.002.007.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Police correspondence, relations, 1995 -- 2013; UA233.002.007.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - President Anthony Monaco, 2010 -- 2015; UA233.002.007.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - President Bacow, 2001 -- 2002; UA233.002.007.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Read by the River, 2000 -- 2009; UA233.002.007.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Risk management, 2008 -- 2009; UA233.002.007.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Risk assessment, 2012; UA233.002.007.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Sexual misconduct policy, 2014; UA233.002.007.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Signage, 1980 -- 2004; UA233.002.007.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Sharewood, 1997 -- 2012; UA233.002.007.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Smoke free, 2011 -- 2012; UA233.002.007.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Student activities, 1989 -- 2012; UA233.002.007.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Student events - Spring Fling/Tuftonia's day 3, 2014 -- 2016; UA233.002.007.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - TAB (Tufts Administration Building) misc., 2000 -- 2016; UA233.002.007.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - TAB (Tufts Administration Building) Somerville, 1988 -- 1991; UA233.002.007.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - TCC - Tufts Community Cares, 2010; UA233.002.008.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Tisch College misc., 2007 -- 2014; UA233.002.008.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Tisch College UCCPS 1, 1993 -- 2014; UA233.002.008.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Tisch College UCCPS 3, 2005 -- 2014; UA233.002.008.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Tisch College UCCPS community programs, 1992 -- 2004; UA233.002.008.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Tisch College UCCPS committee and staff info, 1988 -- 2013; UA233.002.008.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Tisch Library, 1984 -- 2009; UA233.002.008.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - TLC - Tufts Literacy Corp., 2007 -- 2009; UA233.002.008.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Tot-lot Powderhouse Boulevard, 1980 -- 1992; UA233.002.008.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Training and development for faculty, 2001 -- 2004; UA233.002.008.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - TUCC (Tufts University Center for Children), 2010; UA233.002.008.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Tufts Civic Leadership, 1993 -- 2007; UA233.002.008.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - TCRC (Tisch College Community Research Center), 2007 -- 2012; UA233.002.008.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - TCRC (Tisch College Community Research Center), 2005 -- 2008; UA233.002.008.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Tufts International Center, 1992 -- 1999; UA233.002.008.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Tufts Sesquicentennial, 2002; UA233.002.008.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Tufts Student Resources, 1982 -- 1986; UA233.002.008.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Tutoring, 2006 -- 2007; UA233.002.008.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Department of Urban and Environmental Planning, 1998 -- 2011; UA233.002.008.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - UR action planning committee, 2011; UA233.002.008.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Vet School, 1984 -- 2015; UA233.002.009.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Volunteer Prog. - fliers and notes, 1996 -- 2001; UA233.002.009.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Walnut Hill, 2013 -- 2015; UA233.002.009.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - President, 2000 -- 2011; UA233.002.009.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - DiBaiggio report, 1992; UA233.002.009.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Bio-Tech, 1994; UA233.002.009.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Rubel files, 1971 -- 2017; UA233.000029
    This sub-series is arranged in received order.
    This sub-series contains subject files created or collected by former Director Barbara Rubel. Topics include Tufts buildings; policies; committees and associations within and outside Tufts; events and programming within Tufts and within neighborhood communities; and construction projects. This sub-series also contains awards received by the department and aerial photographs of Medford, MA.
    - Boston comm. benefits, 1983 -- 1994; UA233.002.021.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Center for Public Service, 1987 -- 1989; UA233.002.021.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Committee on Fraternities and Sororities, 1989 -- 2002; UA233.002.021.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Chinatown, 1994 -- 1998; UA233.002.021.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Tufts in Chinatown masterplan (legal), 1994 -- 1997; UA233.002.021.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Chinatown, 1971 -- 2003; UA233.002.021.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Committee on Social Fraternities and Sororities, 1988 -- 1994; UA233.002.021.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Context newsletter, 1991 -- 1992; UA233.002.021.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Jones thesis, 1986; UA233.002.021.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Hillside dorm and Medford conflict, 1985 -- 1993; UA233.002.021.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Internships, 1975 -- 1978; UA233.002.021.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Jumbo stampede, 1979 -- 1984; UA233.002.021.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Legal/documents, 2000 -- 2002; UA233.002.021.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Directory of community relations, 1991; UA233.002.021.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Tufts master plan/Boston, 1990 -- 1997; UA233.002.021.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Community and construction, 1973 -- 2018; UA233.002.021.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - M.H.E.F.A, 1988 -- 1991; Ua233.002.021.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Off campus materials, 1979 -- 2007; UA233.002.022.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Abraham Lincoln exhibit, 2005; UA233.002.022.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Problem houses, 2017; UA233.002.022.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Pre-agreement information, 1989; UA233.002.022.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Proposals (1 of 2), 1988 -- 2002; UA233.002.022.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Proposals (2 of 2), 1995 -- 2001; UA233.002.022.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Reports, 1992 -- 2003; UA233.002.022.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Somerville Schools project, 1983 -- 1985; UA233.002.022.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - High school curriculum "crisis", 1983 -- 1985; UA233.002.022.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Student life, 2016 -- 2017; UA233.002.022.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Somerville cable, 1972 -- 1989; UA233.002.022.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Tobacco free initiative, 2014; UA233.002.022.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - "These words" pamphlet, 2016; UA233.002.022.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - TCRC (Tisch College Community Research Center), 2005 -- 2016; UA233.002.022.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - TCRC (Tisch College Community Research Center) grant proposals, 2016 -- 2017; UA233.002.022.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Gentrification, 2014 -- 2015; UA233.002.022.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - TCRC (Tisch College Community Research Center), 2008 -- 2016; UA233.002.022.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Telecommunications, 1988 -- 1999; UA233.002.022.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Aerial photographs, Tufts and Medford, 1981 -- 1983; UA233.002.SB147.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box Shared 147, Folder 9)
    - Award certificates, 1980 -- 2013; UA233.002.SB147.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box Shared 147, Folder 10)
    - South Station project, 1999; UA233.002.SB147.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box Shared 147, Folder 11)
- Campus files, 1973 -- 2016; UA233.003; 3.58 Linear Feet 3 record cartons and 1 12" LP box
  This series is arranged in received order, roughly alphabetically.
  This series contains files relating to the Tufts University campus in the Chinatown neighborhood of Boston, MA, and the Tufts University campus straddling Medford and Somerville, MA. These files include information relating to financial support for each campus; events and programs sponsored by Tufts to engage the local community; letters and requests from neighborhood residents; information relating to city and local governments; historical information on each neighborhood; and planning and project information.
  - Asian American Civic Association, 1998 -- 2011; UA233.003.010.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Asian Community Development Corporation, 2008 -- 2010; UA233.003.010.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - August Moon Festival, 1998 -- 2001; UA233.003.010.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - August Moon Festival, 2002; UA233.003.010.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - August Moon Festival, 2003; UA233.003.010.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - August Moon Festival, 2004; UA233.003.010.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - August Moon Festival--various, 2008 -- 2009; UA233.003.010.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - BCNC (Boston Chinatown Neighborhood Center), 2015 -- 2015; UA233.003.010.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Boston Chinatown misc., 1998 -- 2006; UA233.003.010.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Boston miscellaneous, 2002 -- 2014; UA233.003.010.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - CCEC, 2006; UA233.003.010.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Chinatown land trust, 2015; UA233.003.010.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Chinatown library, 2009 -- 2011; UA233.003.010.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Chinatown main street, 2005 -- 2011; UA233.003.010.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Chinatown master plan, 2008; UA233.003.010.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Chinatown neighbor letters and requests, 2009; UA233.003.010.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Chinatown Oak Street fair, 2002 -- 2009; UA233.003.010.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Chinatown reception, 1993; UA233.003.010.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Chinatown Neighborhood Council, 1998 -- 2015; UA233.003.010.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - CRA newsletter, 2008; UA233.003.010.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - CRA proposal, 2012; UA233.003.010.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Chinatown support FY15, 2014 -- 2015; UA233.003.010.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Chinatown support FY16, 2015 -- 2016; UA233.003.010.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Chinatown support FY16 cont'd, 2015 -- 2016; UA233.003.010.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Chinatown support FY14, 2013 -- 2014; UA233.003.010.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Chinatown support FY14 cont'd, 2013 -- 2014; UA233.003.010.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Chinatown support FY15 cont'd, 2014 -- 2015; UA233.003.010.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Chinatown YMCA, 2003 -- 2012; UA233.003.010.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Chinese Consolidated Benevolent Association, 1990 -- 2012; UA233.003.010.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Chinese Historical Society, 1991 -- 2012; UA233.003.010.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Chinese Progressive Association, 2001 -- 2016; UA233.003.010.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Greater Boston Chinese Golden Age Center, 2003 -- 2016; UA233.003.010.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Lower Washington Street Neighborhood Taskforce, 1999 -- 2002; UA233.003.010.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Lower Washington Street Neighborhood Taskforce 2, 1999; UA233.003.010.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Chinatown donations (not by comm. relations), 2008 -- 2013; UA233.003.010.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - South Cover Community Health Center, 1998 -- 2002; UA233.003.010.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Boys and Girls Club Medford Judging, 2014; UA233.003.011.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Boys and Girls Clubs, Middlesex City, 2016; UA233.003.011.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Building the Future Committee, 1997; UA233.003.011.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - CACHE - Medford, 2010 -- 2013; UA233.003.011.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Condon Shell, 2009; UA233.003.011.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Jingle Bell Festival, 2004; UA233.003.011.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Jingle Bell Festival, 2008 -- 2009; UA233.003.011.00043; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Krystle Campbell Peace Garden, 2015; UA233.003.011.00044; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Medford Arts Council, 1984 -- 1989, 2015; UA233.003.011.00045; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Medford Chamber of Commerce, 2008 -- 2010; UA233.003.011.00046; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Medford Chevalier Auditorium, 1980 -- 1982, 2005, 2014; UA233.003.011.00047; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Medford City Council, 2005 -- 2015; UA233.003.011.00048; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Medford Family Resource, 1995 -- 2000; UA233.003.011.00049; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Medford Family Resource Center, 2001 -- 2004; UA233.003.011.00050; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Medford Family Resource Center, 2005; UA233.003.011.00051; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Medford Health Matters, 2015; UA233.003.011.00052; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Medford High School, 1989 -- 2014; UA233.003.011.00053; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Historical Site Committee - Medford, 1980 -- 1998, 2016; UA233.003.011.00054; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - History - Medford, Curtis House, 1992 -- 1995, 2014; UA233.003.011.00055; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - History - Medford, general information, 1992 -- 1996; UA233.003.011.00056; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - History - Medford, Royall House, 1990 -- 2015; UA233.003.011.00057; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Medford Leap, 2012; UA233.003.011.00058; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Linkage Program Fee - Medford, 1990; UA233.003.011.00059; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Medford Mayor McGlynn, 1991 -- 2016; UA233.003.011.00060; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Medford misc., 1995 -- 2006, 2009, 2016; UA233.003.011.00061; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Medford nuisance ordinances, 2011; UA233.003.011.00062; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Medford parking program, 2014; UA233.003.011.00063; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Medford police, 1994 -- 2002, 2015; UA233.003.011.00064; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Medford politicians - congratulatory notes, 2015 -- 2016; UA233.003.011.00065; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Medford schools, 2003 -- 2015; UA233.003.011.00066; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Medford support FY13, 2012 -- 2013; UA233.003.011.00067; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Medford support FY14, 2013 -- 2014; UA233.003.011.00068; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Medford support FY15, 2014 -- 2015; UA233.003.011.00069; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Medford Traffic Commission, 1989 -- 1994, 2009; UA233.003.011.00070; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Medford Zoning - ordinances, 1997, 2009; UA233.003.011.00071; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - MyRWA, 2013 -- 2016; UA233.003.011.00072; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Neighbor correspondence, 1999, 2009, 2014; UA233.003.011.00073; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Public Library - Dark Tide, 2009; UA233.003.011.00074; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Springstep, 2004, 2008; UA233.003.011.00075; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - West Medford Community Center, 2003, 2007, 2015; UA233.003.011.00076; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Winthrop Street traffic calming 6/12, 2012; UA233.003.012.00077; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Voices of Medford, 2009 -- 2010; UA233.003.012.00078; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Brown School/Tufts Collaborative, 1994 -- 1996; UA233.003.012.00079; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Capital Projects Management Department: Powderhouse School, 2005; UA233.003.012.00080; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - CDBG 2016, UA233.003.012.00081; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Davis Square hotel study, 2006; UA233.003.012.00082; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Department of Education Grant, 1991; UA233.003.012.00083; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - East Somerville Community School fire and rebuilding, 2007; UA233.003.012.00084; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Edgerly School, 2000; UA233.003.012.00085; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Food trucks, 2012 -- 2013; UA233.003.012.00086; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 10)